<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Detroit</string>

    <!-- Drawer Items -->
    <string name="popular_places">Popular Places</string>
    <string name="hotels">Hotels</string>
    <string name="museums">Museums</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="theaters">Theaters</string>
    <string name="information">Information</string>
    <string name="map">Map</string>

    <!-- Popular Places -->
    <string name="fort_wayne">Fort Wayne</string>
    <string name="fort_wayne_details">Fort Wayne is located in the city of Detroit, Michigan, at the foot of Livernois Avenue in the Delray neighborhood. The fort is situated on the Detroit River at a point where it is about a mile to the Canadian shore.</string>
    <string name="fort_wayne_address">6325 W Jefferson Ave, Detroit, MI 48209</string>
    <string name="fort_wayne_number">Phone: (313) 628-0796</string>

    <string name="pewabic_pottery">Pewabic Pottery</string>
    <string name="pewabic_pottery_details">Pewabic Pottery is a ceramic studio and school at 10125 East Jefferson Avenue, Detroit, Michigan. Founded in 1903, the studio is known for its iridescent glazes, some of which grace notable buildings such as the Shedd Aquarium and Basilica of the National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception. The pottery continues in operation today, and was designated a National Historic Landmark in 1991.</string>
    <string name="pewabic_pottery_address">10125 E Jefferson Ave, Detroit, MI 48214</string>
    <string name="pewabic_pottery_number">Phone: (313) 626-2000</string>

    <string name="renaissance_center">GM Renaissance Center</string>
    <string name="renaissance_center_details">The Renaissance Center is a group of seven interconnected skyscrapers in Downtown Detroit, Michigan, United States. Located on the International Riverfront, the Renaissance Center complex is owned by General Motors as its world headquarters.</string>
    <string name="renaissance_center_address">Detroit, MI 48243</string>
    <string name="renaissance_center_number">Phone: (313) 567-3126</string>

    <string name="henry_ford_estate">Henry Ford Estate</string>
    <string name="henry_ford_estate_details">Fair Lane was the name of the estate of Ford Motor Company founder Henry Ford and his wife, Clara Ford, in Dearborn, Michigan, in the United States.</string>
    <string name="henry_ford_estate_address">1 Fair Ln Dr, Dearborn, MI 48128</string>
    <string name="henry_ford_estate_number">Phone: (313) 668-3200</string>

    <string name="comerica_park">Comerica Park</string>
    <string name="comerica_park_details">Comerica Park is an open-air ballpark located in Downtown Detroit. It serves as the home of the Detroit Tigers of Major League Baseball, replacing Tiger Stadium in 2000.</string>
    <string name="comerica_park_address">2100 Woodward Ave, Detroit, MI 48201</string>
    <string name="comerica_park_number">Phone: (313) 962-4000</string>

    <string name="detroit_public_library">Main | Detroit Public Library</string>
    <string name="detroit_public_library_details">The Detroit Public Library is the second largest library system in the U.S. state of Michigan by volumes held (after the University of Michigan Library) and is the 21st largest library system (and the fourth-largest public library system) in the United States. It is composed of the Main Library on Woodward Avenue, which houses the library\'s administration offices, and 23 branch locations across the city. The Main Library is part of Detroit's Cultural Center Historic District listed in the National Register of Historic Places adjacent to Wayne State University campus and across from the Detroit Institute of Arts.</string>
    <string name="detroit_public_library_address">5201 Woodward Ave, Detroit, MI 48202</string>
    <string name="detroit_public_library_number">Phone: (313) 481-1300</string>

    <string name="greektown">Greektown</string>
    <string name="greektown_details">Greektown is a historic commercial and entertainment district in Detroit, Michigan, located just northeast of the heart of downtown, along Monroe Avenue between Brush and St. Antoine Streets with a station on the city\'s elevated downtown transit system known as the Detroit People Mover. Greektown is also situated between the Renaissance Center, Comerica Park, and Ford Field. The district is dominated by Greek-themed restaurants and includes St. Mary Roman Catholic Church, Second Baptist Church, the Athenium Suite Hotel, and the Greektown Casino-Hotel within its boundaries.</string>
    <string name="greektown_address">Greektown, Detroit, MI</string>
    <string name="greektown_number">No Number</string>

    <!-- Hotels -->
    <string name="aloft_hotel">Aloft Detroit at The David Whitney</string>
    <string name="aloft_hotel_details">Aloft Hotels is a hotel chain based in North America, owned by Starwood Hotels &amp; Resorts Worldwide (which was acquired by Marriott International in October 2016), although it is referred to as "a vision of W Hotels". The first hotel opened at the Trudeau International Airport in Montreal in 2008.Aloft Hotels have since opened across North America and internationally.</string>
    <string name="aloft_hotel_address">One, Park Ave, Detroit, MI 48226</string>
    <string name="aloft_hotel_number">Phone: (313) 237-1700</string>

    <string name="mgm_grand_hotel">MGM Grand Detroit</string>
    <string name="mgm_grand_hotel_details">The MGM Grand Detroit is one of three casino resort hotels in Detroit, Michigan, and one of four in the Detroit–Windsor area. The luxury resort hotel opened on July 29, 1999, with a grand event which included models and celebrities including Ashanti, Kid Rock, and fireworks. It is the first luxury casino resort hotel in a major metropolis outside Las Vegas. Detroit is one of the largest American cities and metropolitan regions to offer casino resort hotels.</string>
    <string name="mgm_grand_hotel_address">1777 3rd Ave, Detroit, MI 48226</string>
    <string name="mgm_grand_hotel_number">Phone: (877) 888-2121</string>

    <string name="westin_hotel">Westin Book Cadillac Hotel</string>
    <string name="westin_hotel_details">The Westin Book Cadillac Detroit is a historic skyscraper hotel located at 1114 Washington Boulevard in Downtown Detroit, Michigan, within the Washington Boulevard Historic District. Designed in the Neo-Renaissance style, and constructed as the Book-Cadillac, it is part of Westin Hotels and embodies Neo-Classical elements and building sculpture, incorporating brick and limestone.</string>
    <string name="westin_hotel_address">1114 Washington Blvd, Detroit, MI 48226</string>
    <string name="westin_hotel_number">Phone: (313) 442-1600</string>

    <string name="inn_on_ferry_street">The Inn on Ferry Street</string>
    <string name="inn_on_ferry_street_details">Located in the East Ferry Street Historic District of Midtown Detroit, The Inn on Ferry Street sets the standard for elegant guest quarters and dedicated service. Just steps from the state\’s finest museums, acclaimed Detroit Medical Center and Wayne State University, the Inn is a relaxing change of pace from the standard business hotel.  Consisting of four restored Victorian homes, and two carriage houses the Inn abounds in sophisticated luxury. The Inn On Ferry Street has beautifully maintained landscaping and stunning public spaces.</string>
    <string name="inn_on_ferry_street_address">84 E Ferry St, Detroit, MI 48202</string>
    <string name="inn_on_ferry_street_number">Phone: (313) 871-6000</string>

    <string name="crowne_plaza_hotel">Crowne Plaza Hotel</string>
    <string name="crowne_plaza_hotel_details">The Plaza Land Company was established in 1955 to construct a modern hotel on a site adjacent to the planned Convention Hall and Exhibits Building. In 1956, the company announced a partnership with Conrad Hilton to construct a $24 million hotel, to be named the Pontchartrain Hilton. However the Hilton Hotels Board vetoed the deal in 1960, after which the Plaza Land Company turned to Samuel and Aaron Gershenson\'s Downtown Investment Company, which assumed control of the project.</string>
    <string name="crowne_plaza_hotel_address">2 Washington Blvd, Detroit, MI 48226</string>
    <string name="crowne_plaza_hotel_number">Phone: (313) 965-0200</string>

    <string name="doubletree_suites">DoubleTree Suites</string>
    <string name="doubletree_suites_details">This historic DoubleTree Suites by Hilton Hotel Detroit Downtown - Fort Shelby offers modern all-suite accommodations in the heart of the city. Having recently undergone major refurbishment, our large suites average over 650 sq. ft. and offer more space than many other hotels in Detroit. With complimentary internet access and complimentary shuttle, DoubleTree will keep you connected online and around town.</string>
    <string name="doubletree_suites_address">525 W Lafayette Blvd, Detroit, MI 48226</string>
    <string name="doubletree_suites_number">Phone: (313) 963-5600</string>

    <string name="holiday_inn">Holiday Inn Express &amp; Suites Detroit Downtown</string>
    <string name="holiday_inn_details">Stay Smart at the Holiday Inn Express Hotel &amp; Suites of Downtown Detroit, a perfect location for the business or leisure traveler. In addition to our finely appointed guest rooms. Some of our outstanding amenities include a state-of-the-art fitness Center, indoor heated pool, &amp; 24-hour business center.</string>
    <string name="holiday_inn_address">1020 Washington Blvd, Detroit, MI 48226</string>
    <string name="holiday_inn_number">Phone: (313) 887-7000</string>

    <string name="red_roof_inn">Red Roof Inn Detroit</string>
    <string name="red_roof_inn_details">Red Roof Inn Detroit – Dearborn Greenfield Village is a 100% smoke-free inn that offers free Wi-Fi and flat screen TVs in all guestrooms as well as Grab &amp; Go Breakfast bags. We are just 11 miles from downtown Detroit sports venues, theaters and casinos as well as only 15 miles away from Little Caesars Arena! Our hotel has 90 deluxe rooms and we are within walking distance of several restaurants. Providing easy access to downtown Detroit and the Detroit Metro Airport.</string>
    <string name="red_roof_inn_address">24130 Michigan Ave, Dearborn, MI 48124</string>
    <string name="red_roof_inn_number">Phone: (313) 278-9732</string>

    <string name="comfort_inn">Comfort Inn Near Greenfield Village</string>
    <string name="comfort_inn_details">The Comfort Inn Near Greenfield Village is a Dearborn, MI hotel near top businesses and attractions.</string>
    <string name="comfort_inn_address">20061 Michigan Ave, Dearborn, MI 48124</string>
    <string name="comfort_inn_number">Phone: (313) 436-9600</string>

    <!-- Museums -->
    <string name="detroit_institute_of_arts">Detroit Institute of the Arts</string>
    <string name="detroit_institute_of_arts_details">The Detroit Institute of Arts (DIA), located in Midtown Detroit, Michigan, has one of the largest and most significant art collections in the United States. With over 100 galleries, it covers 658,000 square feet (61,100 m2) with a major renovation and expansion project completed in 2007 that added 58,000 square feet (5,400 m2). The DIA collection is regarded as among the top six museums in the United States with an encyclopedic collection which spans the globe from ancient Egyptian and European works to contemporary art.</string>
    <string name="detroit_institute_of_arts_address">5200 Woodward Ave, Detroit, MI 48202</string>
    <string name="detroit_institute_of_arts_number">Phone: (313) 833-7900</string>

    <string name="henry_ford_museum">Henry Ford Museum</string>
    <string name="henry_ford_museum_details">The Henry Ford (also known as the Henry Ford Museum of American Innovation and Greenfield Village, and more formally as the Edison Institute) is a large indoor and outdoor history museum complex and a National Historic Landmark in the Detroit suburb of Dearborn, Michigan, United States. The museum collection contains the presidential limousine of John F. Kennedy, Abraham Lincoln\'s chair from Ford's Theatre, Thomas Edison\'s laboratory, the Wright Brothers\' bicycle shop, the Rosa Parks bus, and many more historical exhibits.</string>
    <string name="henry_ford_museum_address">20900 Oakwood Blvd, Dearborn, MI 48124</string>
    <string name="henry_ford_museum_number">Phone: (313) 982-6001</string>

    <string name="greenfield_village">Greenfield Village</string>
    <string name="greenfield_village_details">Greenfield Village is a former conditional Amtrak station in Dearborn, Michigan, served by the Wolverine. It was a stop for the Henry Ford Museum and was only used for reserved tour groups of 20 or more people, thus making it one of Amtrak\'s least-busy stations. Prior to 2006, the station was a regular, but seasonal stop (summer only).</string>
    <string name="greenfield_village_address">Dearborn, MI 48124</string>
    <string name="greenfield_village_number">Phone: 313-982-6001</string>

    <string name="motown_museum">Motown Museum</string>
    <string name="motown_museum_details">"Hitsville U.S.A." is the nickname given to Motown\'s first headquarters. A former photographers\' studio located at 2648 West Grand Boulevard in Detroit, Michigan, approaching the New Center area, it was purchased by Motown founder Berry Gordy in 1959.</string>
    <string name="motown_museum_address">1237, 2648 W Grand Blvd, Detroit, MI 48208</string>
    <string name="motown_museum_number">Phone: (313) 875-2264</string>

    <string name="detroit_historical_museum">Detroit Historical Museum</string>
    <string name="detroit_historical_museum_details">The Detroit Historical Museum is located at 5401 Woodward Avenue in the city\'s Cultural Center Historic District in Midtown Detroit</string>
    <string name="detroit_historical_museum_address">5401 Woodward Ave, Detroit, MI 48202</string>
    <string name="detroit_historical_museum_number">Phone: (313) 833-7935</string>

    <string name="african_american_history_museum">Charles H. Wright Museum of African American History</string>
    <string name="african_american_history_museum_details">The Charles H. Wright Museum of African American History is located in the Cultural Center of the U.S. city of Detroit, Michigan. Founded in 1965, the museum holds the world\'s largest permanent exhibit on African-American culture.</string>
    <string name="african_american_history_museum_address">315 E Warren Ave, Detroit, MI 48201</string>
    <string name="african_american_history_museum_number">Phone: (313) 494-5800</string>

    <!-- Parks -->
    <string name="mariner_park">Mariner Park</string>
    <string name="west_riverfront_park">West Riverfront Park</string>
    <string name="grand_circus_park">Grand Circus Park</string>
    <string name="belle_isle">Belle Isle</string>
    <string name="detroit_zoo">Detroit Zoo</string>
    <string name="campus_martius_park">Campus Martius Park</string>
    <string name="state_park_harbor">William G. Milliken State Park and Harbor</string>
    <!-- Restaurants -->
    <string name="giovanni">Giovanni\'s</string>
    <string name="chartreuse">Chartreuse Kitchen &amp; Cocktails</string>
    <string name="supino">Supino Pizzeria</string>
    <string name="selden_standard">Selden Standard</string>
    <string name="buddy_pizza">Buddy\'s Pizza</string>
    <string name="wright_company">Wright &amp; Company</string>
    <string name="mudgies">Mudgie\'s</string>
    <string name="lafayette_coney_island">Lafayette Coney Island</string>
    <string name="vicente">Vicente Cuban Cuisine</string>
    <!-- Theaters -->
    <string name="detroit_opera_house">Detroit Opera House</string>
    <string name="redford_theatre">The Redford Theatre</string>
    <string name="sound_board">Sound Board at MotorCity Casino Hotel</string>
    <string name="masonic_temple">Masonic Temple Theater</string>
    <string name="repertory_theatre">Detroit Repertory Theatre</string>
    <string name="senate_theater">Senate Theater</string>
    <string name="fox_theatre">Fox Theatre</string>
</resources>
